Guide to the Papers of Richard Phillips Feynman, 1933-1988
Archives
- Group II
  - Section I: Correspondence
    - L misc (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Lipkin, Harry 1972-73 (Box 26)
      - List, John 1983 (Box 26)
      - López, Arturo 1977 (Box 26)
      - Lukes, T. 1978 (Box 26)
      - Luttermoser, R. L. 1972 (Box 26)
      - Lynch, Robert E. 1973 (Box 26)
      - Lyntelon [?], Ray 1975 (Box 26)
      - Lyons, Harold 1983 (Box 26)
    - Malina, Frank (Leonardo) 1974-76 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) Press The Character of Physical Law (folder 9) 1966-69; (folder 10) 1970-83 (Box 26, Folder Folders 10-11)
    - Mautner, Leonard and Alix See: Section II, Biographical Miscellany, and Section IV, Mautner Lectures
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company
      - Quantum Mechanics and Path Integrals 1964-67, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence 1986 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - McLellan, William See Section II, Biographical Miscellany
    - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing (3M) 1987 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Mückenheim, W. 1984-86 See also: Routledge and Kegan Paul (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - M misc (2 folders)
      - Mackintosh, A. R. 1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Macomber, J. D. 1974 (Box 26)
      - Malek, S. J. ca 1981 (Box 26)
      - Mancini, Frank P. n.d. (Box 26)
      - Manders, Jeanne 1962, 1973 (Box 26)
      - Mannheim, Philip 1975 (Box 26)
      - Marbois, Richard 1987 (Box 26)
      - Marcus, David 1975-79 (Box 26)
      - Marneus, Shirley 1977 (Box 26)
      - Marsh, Antony R. 1972 (Box 26)
      - Martin, Brian 1987 (Box 26)
      - Martin, George M. 1979 (Box 26)
      - Martin, Richard M. See: Xerox Corporation (Box 26)
      - Mathematical Association of America 1965 (Box 26)
      - McCalley, Karl 1984 (Box 26)
      - McClellan, Larry 1979 (Box 26)
      - McConnell, R. A. 1983-84 (Box 26)
      - McConnell, William L. 1975 (Box 26)
      - McEwan, Stephanie A. 1980 (Box 26)
      - McKay, John 1979 (Box 26)
      - McGill, William See: Columbia University (Box 26)
      - McNift, Virginia 1975 (Box 26)
      - Megee, Robert 1987 (Box 26)
      - Melbourne High School 1965 (Box 26)
      - Mermin, David 1984 (Box 26)
      - Messing, Fredric 1977 (Box 26)
      - Michel, Curtis 1975 (Box 26)
      - Miles, John W. 1982 (Box 26)
      - Miller, B. G. 1975 (Box 26)
      - Miller, R. T. 1974 (Box 26)
      - Milton, Kim 1978 (with photo) (Box 26)
      - Minguillon, Mark 1976 (Box 26)
      - Minicon 1987 (Box 26)
      - Mitescu, Catalin See: Pomona College (Box 26)
      - Mitra, P. 1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Miyazawa, H. 1985 (Box 26)
      - Moeller, Charles R. 1985 (Box 26)
      - Moore, Maxine Ruth (and various aliases) 1975-82 (Box 26)
      - Moore, Richard 1977-78 (Box 26)
      - Morris, Robert 1976 (Box 26)
      - Morrison, Douglas R. O. 1976 (Box 26)
      - Morrison, Philip 1972 (Box 26)
      - Moss, Arthur 1974 (Box 26)
      - Muir, John, High School See: Sallee (Box 26)
      - Muldowney, P. 1982 (Box 26)
      - Muller, Richard 1979 (Box 26)
      - Munger, Edwin 1975 (Box 26)
      - Myers, John M. 1978 (Box 26)
    - Nemec, Donald 1975-83 (out-of-body experiments) See also: Section VIII (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Nobel Prize See: Section II
    - Norton, W. W. and Company, Inc.
      - Surely You're Joking, Mr. Feynman (folder 1) Correspondence and documents 1983-87; (folder 2) Reviews (Box 27, Folder Folders 1-2)
      - What Do You Care What Other People Think? 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - N misc (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Naidis, Mark 1975 (Box 27)
      - National Energy Foundation 1985 (Box 27)
      - Nauenberg, Uriel 1973 (Box 27)
      - Neusner, Jacob 1987 (Box 27)
      - Neva, William 1975 (Box 27)
      - Newman, Joan T. 1986 (Box 27)
      - Newman, Thomas H. 1985-86 (Box 27)
      - Newsweek 1975 (Box 27)
      - New York Academy of Sciences 1987 (Box 27)
      - Nielsen, Ole H. See: Xerox Corporation (Box 27)
      - Nippell, Janet See: Yandell, Ben (Box 27)
      - Nishikawa, Tetsuji 1981 (Box 27)
      - Nissim-Sabat, Charles 1982 (Box 27)
      - Nosanov, L. H. See: Zimmerman, W. (Box 27)
      - Novaco, Anthony D. 1976 (Box 27)
      - Novros, Lester 1975 (Box 27)
      - Nuttall, David 1975 (Box 27)
      - Nylander, James 1987 (Box 27)
    - Oppenheimer, Frank 1974, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Organization of American States (OAS), Mexico Trip 1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Onsager, Lars See: Section II, Nobel Prize
    - O misc (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - O'Conner, Jim n.d. (Box 27)
      - Oehler, Kathy 1974 (Box 27)
      - Okun, Lev 1985-87 See also: Section VI, QED, Russian Edition (Box 27)
      - Olds, R. H. 1985 (Box 27)
      - Olum, Paul 1974 (Box 27)
      - OMNI Publications 1979 (Box 27)
      - Optican, Lance Michael 1969 (Box 27)
      - Orange Unified School District 1984 (Box 27)
      - Ord, Garnet 1982 (Box 27)
      - Osowitz, B. M. 1975 (Box 27)
      - Oxford English Dictionary Supplement 1976 (Box 27)
      - Oxford University Press 1978 (Box 27)
    - Pasadena Unified School District 1976-77 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Pauling, Linus and Ava Helen 1965, 1985-86 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Peierls, Rudolf 1972-73 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Permissions, miscellaneous 1972-87 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Physical Society of Japan 1965-79 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Platzman, Phil 1985 See also: Section VIII (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Princeton University Press, QED: The Strange Theory of Light and Matter
      - Correspondence and documents 1983-88 (with photos) (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Foreign editions 1985-88 See also: Section VI (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Book with Feynman's corrections (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Reviews 1985-87 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Fan and congratulatory mail 1986-87 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - P-Q misc (2 folders)
      - Pacilio, Nicola 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Packard, Richard See: Williams, Gary (Box 28)
      - Page, Don. N. 1978 (Box 28)
      - Page, Ralph 1975 (Box 28)
      - Pagels, Heinz 1974 (Box 28)
      - Paine, Allen 1983 (Box 28)
      - Pakvasa, Sandip 1980 (Box 28)
      - Palmer, Leigh 1987 (Box 28)
      - Palmer, Michael 1974 (Box 28)
      - Parkovic, Marko 1973 (Box 28)
      - Pasadena Public Library 1987 (Box 28)
      - Patera, Elena 1982 (with clipping) (Box 28)
      - Patterson, John W. 1979 (Box 28)
      - Patterson, Neil 1985 (Box 28)
      - Paulson, Dennis 1983 (Box 28)
      - Pell, Erik M. 1976 (Box 28)
      - Petrac, Dusan 1975 (Box 28)
      - Phelan, J. J. 1977 (Box 28)
      - Phillips, Edward 1974 (Box 28)
      - Phillips, Gregory 1973 (Box 28)
      - Physics Review 1977 (Box 28)
      - Piccioni, Oreste 1972, 1978, 1981 (Box 28)
      - Pierce, John R. 1974 (Box 28)
      - Piernick, D. K. 1972 (Box 28)
      - Pierre, Christian 1987 (Box 28)
      - Pines, David 1987 (Box 28)
      - Pipkin, Jill 1975 (Box 28)
      - Pippard, A. B. 1974 (Box 28)
      - See also: Patterson, John W. (Box 28)
      - Plozai, Anthony 1977-78 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Plubell, Philip E. 1976, 1979, 1981 (Box 28)
      - Podell, Howard I. 1987 (Box 28)
      - Pomona College 1974, 1982 (Mitescu, Catalin) (Box 28)
      - Post, Jonathan V. 1982 (Box 28)
      - Post, William D. 1987 (Box 28)
      - Potter, Frank 1984 (Box 28)
      - Precision Film Group 1981 (Box 28)
      - Prescott, Charles 1978 (Box 28)
      - Privateer, Paul 1983 (Box 28)
      - Public Broadcasting Associates 1986 (Box 28)
      - Pugwash Conferences 1982 (Box 28)
      - Quigley, Robert 1972 (Box 28)
    - Reference, letters of, miscellaneous 1972-87 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Riordan, Edward M. 1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Riordan, Michael 1983-85 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Routledge and Kegan Paul, "Negative Probability," in Quantum Theory and Beyond: Essays in Honour of David Bohm Correspondence and documents 1984-85 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - R misc (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Rainwater, James 1975 (Box 28)
      - See also: Section II, Nobel Prize (Box 28)
      - Ramsey, Norman F. 1987 (Box 28)
      - Randell, B. 1972 (Box 28)
      - Rashid, Salim 1974 (Box 28)
      - Ratcliffe, Timothy 1986 (Box 28)
      - Rautenberg, Tom 1981 (Box 28)
      - Read, Gerald H. 1977 (Box 28)
      - Regan, Brian T. 1975 (Box 28)
      - Repovs, Dusan, Jr. 1974 (Box 28)
      - Richardson, F. B. 1981 (Box 28)
      - Richter, Burton 1974 (Box 28)
      - Ritz, Edward F. 1972 (Box 28)
      - Robbins, Howard n.d. (Box 28)
      - Roberts, Jack 1981 (Box 28)
      - Roberts, Nick 1983 (Box 28)
      - Robertson, Brent 1972 (Box 28)
      - Roman, G. 1982 (Box 28)
      - Rose, Augusta 1975 (Box 28)
      - Rose, Jed E. 1987 (Box 28)
      - Rosen, Louis 1974 (Box 28)
      - Rossi, Bruno 1983 (Box 28)
      - Roth, Dana 1980 (Caltech Libraries) (Box 28)
      - Rothfeld, Gloria 1975 (Box 28)
      - Rowe, D. M. 1981 (Box 28)
      - Rucher, Rob 1974 (Box 28)
      - Ruderfer, Martin 1966, 1978 (Box 28)
      - Rumore, Phil n.d. (Box 28)
      - Rutherford, David 1975 (Box 28)
    - Sagan, Carl, Productions 1982-83 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Salam, Abdus 1966 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Schweber, S. S. 1980-85 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Science Magazine: "The Structure of the Proton" Correspondence 1973, 1975, 1985-86 See also: Section V, VI (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Schrödinger, Erwin See: Todd, Olga Taussky
    - Slager, Donald M. 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Student letters (high school and below) 1971-87 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Sutherland, Bill 1987 See also: Section VIII (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - S misc (2 folders) (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Sachs, Mendel 1978 (Box 29)
      - Saetta, Guy T. 1983 (Box 29)
      - Safer, Carol 1982 (Box 29)
      - Safier, Emil 1979 (Box 29)
      - Salk Institute 1974 (Box 29)
      - Sallee, [?] 1983 (John Muir High School) (Box 29)
      - Salvadó, Carlos 1975, n.d. (Box 29)
      - Sands, Matthew 1985 (Box 29)
      - Santilli, Ruggero Maria 1976 (Box 29)
      - Sarfatti, J. 1975 (Esalen) (Box 29)
      - Scheff, Thomas J. 1986 (Box 29)
      - Scherk, Joël 1977 (Box 29)
      - Schlichter, Paul 1982 (Box 29)
      - Schornstein, Bernie 1985 (Box 29)
      - Schultz, Ted 1986 (Box 29)
      - Science Digest 1984 (Box 29)
      - Science Research Associates 1974 (Box 29)
      - Scientific American 1973 (Box 29)
      - Seelig, Wolfgang 1972 (Box 29)
      - Sellers, Rorick 1987 (Box 29)
      - Serbian National Defense Council 1973 (Box 29)
      - Shavran, Rabbi Avi 1987 (Box 29)
      - Shaw, A. 1977 (Box 29)
      - Sheidlower, Jesse 1985 (Box 29)
      - Shinitzky, Meir 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Shirkov, D. V. 1976 (Box 29)
      - Shoulders, K. R. 1986 (Box 29)
      - Simon, Walter 1981-83 (The World of Learning) (Box 29)
      - Sinha, P. M. N. 1975 (Box 29)
      - Sittler, Karl E. 1974 (Box 29)
      - Smith, C. H. Llewellyn 1978 (Box 29)
      - Smith, Jack H. 1981 (Box 29)
      - Smith, Miranda Weston [?] 1974 (Box 29)
      - Smith, Paul K. 1987 (Box 29)
      - Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics 1965 (Box 29)
      - Socolow, Robert H. 1984 (Box 29)
      - Soviet Physics Uspekhi 1975, 1985 (Box 29)
      - Soldini, J. 1987 (Box 29)
      - Spector, N. H. 1985 (Box 29)
      - Springer Verlag 1981 (Box 29)
      - Srivastava, R. 1987 (Box 29)
      - Stachiewicz, Paul 1975 (La Petite Ecole) (Box 29)
      - Stadler, [?] 1987 (Box 29)
      - Stahl, Bob 1965 (Box 29)
      - Stanley, Michael 1975 (Box 29)
      - Steckel, Arthur D. 1986 (Box 29)
      - Stedman, Geoffrey 1982 (Box 29)
      - Stevens, Barry 1984 (Box 29)
      - Stillerman, Ivan 1975 (Box 29)
      - Storm, Gale 1979 (Box 29)
      - Strategic Defense Initiative See: Thorne, Kip (Box 29)
      - Strickland, Glenn G. 1983 (Box 29)
      - Structural Dynamics Research Corp. 1973 (Box 29)
      - Suedfeld, Peter 1975 (Box 29)
      - Sukhatme, Uday 1977 (Box 29)
      - Sweet, Rev. Sanford S. 1976 (Box 29)
      - System Development Foundation 1981 (Box 29)
    - Teitelboim, Claudio 1984-85 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Telegdi, Val 1973-85 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Thinking Machines Corporation 1983-84, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Thornber, Karvel K. 1965, 1969, 1978 See also: Section VIII (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Todd, Olga Taussky n.d. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - T misc (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Tarpley, Christopher 1987 (Box 29)
      - Technion (Israel Institute of Technology) 1979 (Box 29)
      - Temmen, Lüder 1975 (with clipping) (Box 29)
      - Tewary, V. K. 1983 (Box 29)
      - Thillaimuthu, J. 1982 (with photo) (Box 29)
      - Thomas, Arthur 1974 (Box 29)
      - Thomchick, John 1975 (Box 29)
      - Thorne, Kip n.d. See also: Section VIII (Box 29)
      - Thurnauer, Hans 1986 (Box 29)
      - Tigelaar, Howard 1982 (Box 29)
      - Tollestrup, Alvin 1985 (Box 29)
      - Tonomura, Akira 1983 (Box 29)
      - Tournas, Apostolos 1985 (Box 29)
      - Trimble, Virginia 1987 (Box 29)
      - Troyer, James 1974 (Box 29)
      - Truzzi, Marcello 1985 (Box 29)
      - Tryon, E. P. 1974 (Box 29)
      - Tuan, S. F. 1973 See also: Section VIII (Box 29)
      - Turney, Jeanne F. 1975 (Box 29)
      - Tykodi, Ralph J. 1975 (Box 29)
    - Unidentified (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - University of California, miscellaneous 1973-82 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Vanderbroucke, Russell 1984-86 (Los Alamos Revisited) (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - U-V misc (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Uchida, Mie 1978 (Box 29)
      - Ungerleider, Ilene 1975 (Box 29)
      - Valainos [?], John (Box 29)
      - Van Der Hyde, V. A. 1986 (Box 29)
      - Van de Snepscheut, Jan 1984, n.d. See also: Section VIII (Box 29)
      - Van Duykeren, N. W. J. 1973 (Box 29)
      - Van Iderstine, David 1985 (Box 29)
      - Van Nuys High School 1985, n.d. (Box 29)
      - Van Sant, Tom 1985 (Box 29)
      - Vasey, Joel 1975 (Box 29)
      - Vedhanel, Rich 1974 (Box 29)
      - Veneziano, G. 1985 (Box 29)
      - Vilain, Michael 1974 (Box 29)
      - Viliani, Gabriele 1972 (Box 29)
      - Virshup, Gary 1978 (Box 29)
      - Vogelsang, Roger 1975 (Box 29)
      - Vogue 1984 (Box 29)
      - Vu_kovi_, Vera 1982 (Box 29)
    - Weber, Joe 1976, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Weisskopf, Victor 1961, 1976, 1979-80 See also: Section VIII (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Wheeler, John A. 1973, 1977-78 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Kenneth G. 1976, 1982 See also: Section VIII (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Witten, Edward 1982 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Wolff, J. Gerard 1981-82 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Wolfram, Stephen 1981, 1985 See also: Thinking Machines Corporation See also: Section VIII (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Dudley See: Section II, Orbisphere 29.20
    - Wyden, Peter 1983 (Box 29)
    - W misc (2 folders)
      - Wadlinger, Robert L. 1976 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Wahlquist, Hugo 1983 (Box 29)
      - Wallace, A. D. 1965 (Box 29)
      - Walsh, Birrell 1974 (Box 29)
      - Ward, Pat 1986 (Box 29)
      - Warner, Kenneth R., Jr. 1975 (Box 29)
      - Wasserburg, G. J. 1986 (Box 29)
      - Watt, Bob 1986 (Box 29)
      - Weber, Robert L. 1979 (Box 29)
      - Weinberg, Steven 1977 See also: Section VIII (Box 29)
      - Weinstock, Robert 1983 (Box 29)
      - Welch, Marcelle 1984 (Box 29)
      - Wessel, Walter 1971-72 (Box 29)
      - Wheeler, Harvey 1975 (Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions) (Box 29)
      - Whiteley, J. N. 1971 (Box 29)
      - Wickett, Walton 1976 (Box 29)
      - Wiley-Interscience 1974-75 (Box 29)
      - Williams College 1965 (Box 29)
      - Williams, Gary and Richard E. Packard 1974 (Box 29)
      - Williams, Robert C. 1985 (Box 29)
      - Williams, Robert W. 1983 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Williamson, Paul R. 1983 (Box 29)
      - Willis, David 1982 (Box 29)
      - Willis, Harry T. 1975 (Box 29)
      - Wilsdorf, Doris 1972 (Box 29)
      - Wilson, Richard 1983, 1985 (Box 29)
      - Wilson, Robert 1978, 1985 (Box 29)
      - Wilts, James R. 1974 (Box 29)
      - Witonsky, Phil 1986 (Box 29)
      - Wolff, Andrew H. 1974 (Box 29)
      - Wolsson, Kenneth 1981 (Box 29)
      - Wong, Po Kee 1983 (Box 29)
      - Woods, Jean Whitaker 1983 (Box 29)
      - Woodward, Alan 1982 (Box 29)
      - Wouk, Herman 1973 (Box 29)
      - Wu, Yu-hsun 1973 See also: Chou, Pei-yuan (Box 29)
      - Wu, Zi Yi 1984 (Box 29)
      - Wunderman, Irwin 1977 (Box 29)
      - Wybourne, B. G. 1982 (Box 29)
    - Yorkshire Television 1972, 1975-76, 1983 See also: Malina, Frank (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Yukawa, Hideki 1948, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - X-Y-Z misc (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Xerox Corporation 1983 (Ole H. Nielsen and Richard M. Martin) (Box 29)
      - Yacasua, L. T. 1975 (Box 29)
      - Yandell, Ben and Janet Nippell 1982 (Box 29)
      - Young, Fredric 1976 (Box 29)
      - Young, Robert A. 1983 (Box 29)
      - Yourgrau, Wolfgang 1978 (Box 29)
      - Zahlan, A. B. 1965 (Box 29)
      - Zammitt, Norman 1982 (Box 29)
      - Zarmi, Yair 1977 (Box 29)
      - Zeldovich, Y. B. n.d. (Box 29)
      - Zimmer, Stuart 1982 (Box 29)
      - Zimmerman, W. and L. H. Nosanow 1965 (Box 29)
      - Zubov, Victor See: Read, Gerald H. (Box 29)
      - Zweig, George See: Section II, Nobel Prize, Swedish Royal Academy of Science (Box 29)
  - Section II: Biographical
    - Fan mail
      - Miscellaneous 1972, 1979, 1982-87, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - NOVA, miscellaneous 1975-79 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - "The Pleasure of Finding Things Out" (folder 3) Nov 1981-Apr 1982; (folder 4) Jan-June 1983; ( folder 5) Aug 1983-Jan 1984, n.d.; (folder 6) (Box 30, Folder Folders 3-6)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and documents 1981-84
      - "Surely You're Joking" and other books 1983-84, Jan-Mar 1985, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - "Surely You're Joking" and other books (folder 1) Apr-May 1985; (folder 2) June-Aug 1985; (folder 3) Sept-Dec 1985; ( folder 4) Jan-June 1986; (folder 5) July-Dec 1986; (folder 6) Jan-June 1987; (folder 7) July 1987-1988, n.d.; (folder 8) Reviews and miscellaneous correspondence (Box 31, Folder Folders 1-8)
    - Nobel Prize
      - Nobel Foundation, correspondence and documents 1965-68 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Swedish Royal Academy of Science, correspondence and documents 1965-77 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Swedish Broadcasting Corporation, correspondence and documents 1965 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Nobel trip [Dec 1965], miscellaneous correspondence 1965-66 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Ceremonial banquet speech 10 Dec 1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Prize Ceremony, photos Dec 1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Nobel Lecture, "The Development of the Space-Time View of Quantum Electrodynamics" (folder 7) Editorial and miscellaneous correspondence 1965-71; (folder 8) Prints (Box 32, Folder Folders 7-8)
      - Athenaeum dinner 7 Jan 1966 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Feynman to other Nobelists 1967-68 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Alvarez, Luis 1968 (Box 32)
        - Bethe, Hans 1967 (Box 32)
        - Mottelson, Ben 1975 (Box 32)
        - Onsager, Lars 1968 (Box 32)
        - Rainwater, James 1975 (Box 32)
      - Gathering of Nobel Prize Winners 1973, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Printed matter and clippings (Box 32, Folder Folders 12-13)
      - Congratulatory letters
        - A-B (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - C-E (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - F-G (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - H-J (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - K-M (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - N-P (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - R (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - S (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - T-V (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - W-Z (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Anonymous, unidentified, miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Miscellany
      - Arms Control ca 1980-82 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Art Exhibition, Bullock's 1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Biographical data (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Bohr, Niels, Medal 1973 (with newsclips) (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - California Curriculum Commission, "Comments on the New Arithmetic Textbooks" (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Caltech Division of Humanities and Social Sciences, Jenijoy LaBelle 1975-76 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Caltech Division of Physics, Math and Astronomy
        - Appointments and promotions 1973-74 (Box 34, Folder 7)
          - Farrar, Glennys (Box 34)
          - Field, Richard D. (Box 34)
          - Fox, Geoffrey C. (Box 34)
          - Mewaldt, R. (Box 34)
          - Sciulli, Frank (Box 34)
          - Sierk, Arnold J. (Box 34)
          - Werner, Michael (Box 34)
          - Wilson, Kenneth (Box 34)
      - Candidacy exam 1974 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Fairchild nominations 1975 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Caltech leaves of absence 1974-77 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Caltech Libraries and Archives 1968-69, 1986-87 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Cancer and misc. health-related documents 1972-85 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Cartoons and caricatures (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Estephanian, Steven Fabric Cutting Machine (folder 14) 1965; (folder 15) 1972-77 (Box 34, Folder Folders 14-15)
      - Family and friends, miscellaneous personal correspondence (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Far Rockaway High School
        - Correspondence and documents 1965-67 (Box 34, Folder 17)
        - Feynman Lecture Series 1966-67 (Box 34, Folder 18)
        - The Chat (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Financial records, misc. (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Manhattan Project 1945/1973 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Mautner, Alix (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - McLellan micromotor (with photos) 1960 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Miniaturization projects (with photos) 1960-1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Mexico Property 1972-82 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Newsclips, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Personal material, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Printed material, misc. biographical (folder 8) 1950s-60s; (folder 9) 1970s-80s (Box 35, Folder Folders 8-9)
      - Rhodes, C. K., Neutrino Detection (Atlantic Richfield Co.) 1980 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Sketches (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Sketch pad (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Tuva trip and film 1981-82, 1986-88 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Welton, Theodore "Memories" (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Zorthian, Jirayr H. "Surely it isn't Science" 1987 (incomplete) (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Orbisphere Corporation/Laboratories
      - Dudley Wright, Personal Correspondence (folder 1) 1978-81; (folder 2) 1982-83; (folder 3) 1985-87 (Box 36, Folder Folders 1-3)
      - Feynman visit March 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Financial Statements 1979-80, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Board of Directors, Correspondence and Documents 1985-86 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - John Hale, Correspondence and Technical Notes (folder 7) 1979-80; (folder 8) 1981-83; (folder 9) 1984-85, undated (Box 36, Folder Folders 7-9)
      - Dan Gagescu, Correspondences and Technical Notes 1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous Technical Notes (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Documents, Printed Matter (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Section III: Space Shuttle "Challenger" Investigation
    - Correspondence (5 folders)
      - A-F (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - G-H (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - K (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - L-R (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - S-Z (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Feynman's working notes (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Working documents, misc (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Flame analysis, photos and data (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Temperature effects (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Feynman's notes "Temperatures of SRB" [incomplete?] (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Technical material, misc (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Technical material, NASA (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Reports
      - GAO, "Report to Congress" 23 Feb 1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Feynman's notes on Presidential Commission Report (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Feynman's report on "Reliability of the Shuttle" (2 versions) (Box 38, Folder 5)